askthepotato.com 2017-12-17

# AskThePotato: Save money by shopping online for Travel Deals, Computers, Music, Fashion and more

**The AskThePotato.com- Commitment to Privacy:**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Here at the AskThePotato, we're committed to ensuring that all your personal information that is collected is kept private and protected. We make sure that the AskThePotato.com website is absolutely secure in our collection and use of your personal information. 

**What this Privacy and Cookie Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers the AskThePotato.com treatment of personally identifiable information that the AskThePotato.com collects when you use the AskThePotato’s services. 

The policy also gives information about cookies. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the AskThePotato does not own or control, or to people that the AskThePotato does not employ or manage. 

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, the AskThePotato.com gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. 

We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. 

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

**Links to Other Sites**

The AskThePotato.com contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by the AskThePotato.com Please be aware that we, the AskThePotato.com are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

**Security**

In order to maximize protection of your information, the AskThePotato.com Site Manager uses state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts your credit card number as it is transmitted over the Internet. Of course, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure, and the AskThePotato.com does not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data on or through the use of the the AskThePotato.com service is at your own risk. 

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

White Hart Solutions Ltd, 5 Peel Market Place, Isle of Man email us at: [webmaster@AskThePotato.com](mailto:webmaster@AskThePotato.com)
